http://moltox.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Other Reagents
Vogel Bonner Salts (VBE)
Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice describes our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information. It applies to any Molecular Toxicology Inc. (Moltox) site where this Privacy Notice appears and to any Moltox application, service, or tool (collectively "Services") where this Privacy Notice is referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including through mobile devices.
By using our Services and/or registering for an account with us, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Notice and our User Agreement, and you are consenting to our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not provide the information we require, we may not be able to provide all of our services to you.
You are contracting with Molecular Toxicology Inc. (Moltox), P.O. Box 1189, Boone North Carolina 28607, USA
The company you are contracting with is your data controller, and is responsible for the collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information in accordance with our global privacy standards as well as any applicable national laws. We may process and retain your personal information on our servers in the U.S. and elsewhere in the world where our data centers are located.
Personal Information
"Personal information" is information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that specific person whether from that data or from that data and other information that Moltox has or is likely to have access to. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used to identify a specific person, whether in combination with other information or otherwise.
Changes to this Notice
We may amend this Privacy Notice at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are posted. We will announce any material changes to this Privacy Notice via email.
Products
Search
Ames Products
Mutagenicity Assay Kits & Reagents
Prepared Culture Media
Reagents
All Categories
Customer Services
© 2018 Molecular Toxicology Inc.
Web design by Molecular Toxicology Inc.
